DIVYANSHU KORAT

FLUTTER DEVELOPER



+91-82389 35855

korat750@gmail.com

Surat, Gujarat, India

in <u>Divyanshu Korat</u>

PROFILE

Qualified and professional Mobile developer with 5+ years of experience. Mobile app alchemist, transforming ideas into intuitive and engaging experiences. Storyteller with a knack for translating user needs into beautiful and functional apps. Full-stack developer mastering both front-end and back-end development, ensuring seamless app performance.

SKILLS

- Hybrid / Cross-Platform Application
- · Application Design
- Flutter Development
- Front End
- · Problem-Solving
- Computer Literacy
- Project Management
- Strong Communication
- Continuous Integration (CI)
- Continuous Development (CD)

EXPERIENCE

SOFTWARE ENGINEER (FLUTTER)

Intelliquity Consulting Services

May, 2024 - Present

- Implemented Mobile Gold Ownership Platform
- Enhanced Code Quality and Stability
- Agile Development and Code Reviews
- · Continuous Integration Setup
- Advanced Flutter Techniques

FLUTTER DEVELOPER

Provab Technosoft

Feb, 2023 - Jan, 2024

- Accomplishment/Responsibility/Task
- · Analyzed and Improved code stability
- Mentored and empowered a team of junior developers

EDUCATION

BACHELOR OF TECHNOLOGY INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY

Charotar University of Science and Technolgy

2016 - 2019

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER (MOBILE) Dev Information Technology Limited

Aug, 2021 - Nov, 2022

- Estimated Product/Modules
- Maintained project resources
- Client communication
- Appreciated: Software Developer(Mobile) Software Developer(Flutter)

FLUTTER ASSOCIATE DEVELOPER

IBL Infotech

Aug, 2019 - July, 2021

- Managed the structure of the code
- Participated in development life-cycle
- Investigated technologies to make development faster
- Appreciated: Flutter Associate Developer Flutter Developer Flutter Trainee

DIPLOMA INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY

Bhagwan Mahavir University

2013 - 2016

LANGUAGE

English
 Conversational

• Hindi -

Gujarati

Native or Bilingual Proficiency

Native or Bilingual Proficiency